scripttechs.com 2016-11-26

# core.privacy_policy

**Our Privacy Policy  
**   
**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our footer menu. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the ScriptTechs website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information **(by Paypal and maintained by Paypal)**   
Website server and log in information for installations   
IP address 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. We do use Google Analytics and [SparkPost](http://sparkpost.com/) (transactional email service) on this site. Each of those has SEO tools and analytics to see regions and other non personal information. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Other Parties**

There are many members of our community that offer services and help. Our privacy policy is in regards to ScriptTechs and not to private third parties that are members of our community. Before releasing any information to them, please check with their privacy policies. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
**  
Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by going to your account settings and privacy settings. 

**Site Usage Information**

Similar to other commercial web sites, our web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed and time spent at our web site. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [let us know](https://bryzar.zendesk.com/hc/en-us).
